(JinSoul is dancing on the water!)
(Her shoes is wet...)
(Positive) You know, the water splashed when I danced on the water.
It was fun~
And... It's dinner time!
(JinSoul preparing a meal alone...)
(Suddenly the light turned off!)
(Happy Birthday, JinSoul!)
♬Happy birthday dear JinSoul. Happy birthday to you♬
(To celebrate both her birthday and becoming the seventh member of LOOΠΔ,
they prepared two cakes!)
I wish everything goes well with LOOΠΔ!
And... I also wish myself good luck...!
HaSeul: We have to put the cake on her face at least once!
HaSeul: (Seriuos) You better don't do that to me, YeoJin~
HaSeul: (Her wish) Um... shall we do that? 'This has been LOOΠΔ?'
(The 7 released members of LOOΠΔ finally gathered together in front of the camera!)
This has been LOOΠΔ!